<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CyberSecurity</string>
    <string name="welcome">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="aboutApp1">CSAO is an initiative to make the citizens cyber secure under the ages of Digital India Initiative started by the Government of India. Our mission is to aware, guide and educate each individual about cyber frauds that are taking place around them and provide them a piece of advice from renowned cyber experts on the expert panel.
CSAO is a brain child of Ms. Chandni Agarwal, senior IT faculty at Maharaja Agrasen Model School. She has taken this initiative to make cyber se ure society and worked with her team of students taking this step forward to aware all and solve the problems related to cyber world. It is our proud privilege to have Mrs Nisha Dua on our expert panel. </string>
    <string name="preference_file_name">Cyber Security</string>
    <string name="aboutus">About Us</string>
    <string name="appcreator">APP CREATOR TEAM</string>
    <string-array name="data_do">
        <item>@string/do1</item>
        <item>@string/do2</item>
        <item>@string/do3</item>
        <item>@string/do4</item>
        <item>@string/do5</item>
        <item>@string/do6</item>
        <item>@string/do7</item>
        <item>@string/do8</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_dont">
        <item>@string/dont1</item>
        <item>@string/dont2</item>
        <item>@string/dont3</item>
        <item>@string/dont4</item>
        <item>@string/dont5</item>
        <item>@string/dont6</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="do1">Set your browser security to high and add safe websites to trusted website zone..</string>
    <string name="do2">Disable the login and remembering passwords information...</string>
    <string name="do3">Block pop up window in your web browser...</string>
    <string name="do4">"Enable the option “warn me when sites try to install extensions/theme”  in your web browser..</string>
    <string name="do5">Try to have separate email id other than your official id to be  used in social website...</string>
    <string name="do6">Be extremely careful about how you share personal information about yourself online</string>
    <string name="do7">Make sure that your ISP and Internet Relay Chart (IRC) network have an acceptable use policy that prohibits cyber-stalking.</string>
    <string name="do8">Always install recommended updates and install original antivirus and antispyware programs..</string>


    <string name="dont1">Don\'t delete harmful communications (emails, chat logs, posts etc). These may help provide vital information about the identity of the person behind these..</string>
    <string name="dont2">  Do not open e-mail attachments from strangers, regardless of how enticing the subject line or attachment may be..  </string>
    <string name="dont3">  Do not give your password to anybody. Somebody who is malicious can cause great harm to you and your reputation. It is like leaving your house open for a stranger and walking away.  </string>
    <string name="dont4"> Do not copy a program that is copyrighted on the net. It is illegal.   </string>
    <string name="dont5">  When talking to somebody new on the net, do not give away personal information-like numbers of the credit card used by your parents, your home addresses/ phone numbers and such other personal information...  </string>
    <string name="dont6"> Do not open e-mail attachments from strangers, regardless of how enticing the subject line or attachment may be...   </string>



    <string name="complaint1">Register a cyber complaint</string>
    <string name="complaint2">1. This portal facilitates victims/complainants to report cyber crime complaints online.\n2. This portal caters to complaints pertaining to cyber crimes only with special focus on cyber crimes against women and children. \n3. Complaints reported on this portal are dealt by law enforcement agencies/ police based on the information available in the complaints.\n\n It is imperative to provide correct and accurate details while filing complaint for prompt action.</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="complaint9">Citizen Login with the Complaint Name and the required field to track the status of your Complaint</string>
    <string name="complaint8">Report anonymously . Fill in the Complaint/Incident Details and proceed to next steps and do fill all the information correct and carefully
           </string>
    <string name="complaint7">Next step is to choose between Report Cyber Crime Related to Women/Child and Report Other Cyber Crime . Choose appropriately </string>
    <string name="complaint6">Prior to filing a complaint with this portal , you should agree to the Terms and Conditions . Should you have queries prior to filing your complaint, view Frequently Asked Questions FAQ.</string>
    <string name="complaint4">Procedure</string>
    <string name="complaint5">Filing a Complaint on National Cyber Crime Reporting Portal ! Click on File a Complaint to proceed to the next step</string>
    <string name="complaint3">Prior to filing a complaint with this portal, we would request you to read the below information regarding terms and conditions. Should you have queries prior to filing your complaint, view Frequently Asked Questions on the website . Procedure to complete the process is specified below . </string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="info">info</string>
    <string name="dos_and_dont_image">Dos and Dont Image</string>
    <string name="learn_cyber_crime_headings">Learn Cyber Crime Headings</string>
    <string name="linkFAQ">
        <a href="https://cybercrime.gov.in/Default.aspx">Click here to proceed </a>
    </string>
    <string name="getcybersafe">
               <a href="https://www.getcybersafe.gc.ca/">Get Cyber Safe</a>
    </string>
    <string name="icert">
               <a href="https://www.cert-in.org.in/">Indian Computer Emergency Response Team</a>
    </string>
    <string name="isa">
               <a href="https://infosecawareness.in/">Information Security Awareness</a>
    </string>
    <string name="hyderabad">
               <a href="https://hyderabadpolice.gov.in/">Hyderabad City Police</a>
    </string>
    <string name="safetyNetkids">
               <a href="http://www.safetynetkids.org.uk/personal-safety/online-safety/">Safety Net Kids</a>
    </string>
    <string name="cyberpeacefoundation">
               <a href="https://www.cyberpeace.org/">Cyber Peace Foundation</a>
    </string>
    <string name="ciet">
               <a href="https://ciet.nic.in/">Central Institute of Educational Technology</a>
    </string>


    <string name="cyberswachhtakendra">
        <a href="https://www.cyberswachhtakendra.gov.in/">Cyber Swachhta Kendra</a>
    </string>
    <string name="cyberswachhtakendrasecuritytools">
        <a href="https://www.cyberswachhtakendra.gov.in/security-tools.html">Cyber Swachhta Kendra Security Tools</a>
    </string>
    <string name="cyberattacks">
        <a href="https://www.infosecawareness.in/article/covid19-cyber-attacks">Covid19 Cyber Attacks</a>
    </string>
    <string name="cyberthreats">
        <a href="https://www.interpol.int/Crimes/Cybercrime/COVID-19-cyberthreats">COVID-19 Cyber Threats</a>
    </string>
    <string name="cyberSandS">
        <a href="https://ciet.nic.in/upload/cyber%20safety%20and%20security.pdf">Cyber Safety And Security</a>
    </string>
    <string name="studentsecurity">
        <a href="https://ciet.nic.in/upload/Cyber%20Security%20for%20Students.pdf">Cyber Security for Students</a>
    </string>
    <string name="teacherguidelines">
        <a href="http://www.ncert.nic.in/pdf_files/Guidelines_Teachers.pdf">Cyber Security Teacher Guidelines</a>
    </string>

    <string name="do_string">
        DO
    </string>
    <string name="dont_string">
        DONT
    </string>
    <string name="webinar">
                <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLD5wzl-GmKMVrfli48k0ypE6HtrGO_sP-"> Click here </a>

    </string>
</resources>